I don't think I understand how much build up there was for that cow statue.
So we're here at the DMZ, which is basically the militarized zone, the 38th parallel.
It's just crazy to think that a country was just separated because some people were going to capitalize off of it.
You know, it's never worth it.
It's perfect.
End of separation, beginning of unification.
So after enduring a seven minute video that was more propaganda than even Shen Yun, I decided
not to venture into the tunnels that are being presented to us as clandestine efforts made
by North Korea to invade South Korea.
So I'm going to take a nap.
So the demilitarized zone is basically characterized as the space between the 38th parallel and where civilians are allowed to cross.
So there's like the 38th parallel and then there's lines on each side of North Korea and South Korea that extend beyond the 38th parallel.
Kind of like a continental shelf, if you will, where like you can't cross.
You're like 3-0.
So I'm going to come back.
I'm going to go back.
Bye!
We're done with the stars!
Next time, blue and white.
Look at the stars, guys.
Oh my God.
You're looking good.
Please get your stars.
Support a real one.
Hold on the light.
Hey, you're looking good.
You're looking good.
Well, I'm looking good.
It's too late.
See ya.
You're looking good.
I'm looking good.
But you're looking good.
Yeah.
No.
I'm looking good.
What I'm looking good at you.